icewalkers.com 2014-06-29

# IceWalkers.com - Privacy Policy

**Respect for privacy**

We at www.icewalkers.com are committed to respecting your privacy. Our privacy policy is in place to assure you that we will responsibly protect and manage personally identifiable information you share with us. 

**Protecting visitor information**

In general, you can visit www.icewalkers.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the browser' domain name and IP address and analyze the aggregate data for statistics, but individual users remain anonymous. 

**Your consent**

We ask visitors to provide personal information such as email-address for the purpose of registering an username or to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you how we will use the information. We will not sell your personal information to third parties without explicitly asking for and receiving your permission. We will also take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. 

You always have the option not to provide personal information, in which case you can still visit the public areas of IceWalkers web site. However, you may be unable to access certain options and services. 

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are identifiers which a website can send to your browser and keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to a site. Most cookies expire by themselves after a short period of time. Our web pages may utilize cookies only for the purpose of authenticating your current session while you are logged in. We do not transfer any cookie information to other sites. 

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there are simple procedure to manually delete your cookies and to configure your browser to refuse them. Please consult your web browser's help documentation for more information. 

**Third Party Cookies**

We use Google Adsense, Tribal Fusion, DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. In the course of ads being served on this website, these companies may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by some of these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

For more information about Google privacy policy please click [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). 

For more information about Tribal Fusion privacy policy please click [here](http://www.tribalfusion.com/www/about/privacy.html). 

**Commitment**

We are committed to privacy and to the preservation of individual privacy rights on the Internet. www.icewalkers.com strives to meet the ever-changing demands of personal data privacy as they arise. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy.policy@icewalkers.com](mailto:privacy.policy@www.icewalkers.com) .
